Finding Aid for the Recordings of Creative Associates Recitals, 1964-1980
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel to reel tapes, 1964-1980, I.; Reel 1-Reel 172
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 37, February 15, 1969, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 6, Reel 067)
    Work number: ubmu0063_067_03
    Xenakis, Iannis
    Herma (1960-61)
    Duration: 7:12
    Cassette backup: CA 222
    Work number: ubmu0063_067_04
    Takahashi, Yuji
    Chromamorphe 2 (1964)
    Duration: 6:58
    Cassette backup: CA 223
    Work number: ubmu0063_067_05
    Time (1962), film soundtrack
    Performers: Joseph Romanowski, electronic assistant
    Duration: 8:25
    Cassette backup: CA 224
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 38, February 27, 1969, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 6, Reel 068)
    Work number: ubmu0063_068_01
    Cantata no. 36: Schwingt freudig euch empor. Auch, mit gedampften schwachen Stimmen
    Performers: Mary Beth Peil, soprano; Charles Haupt, violin; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 7:14
    Cassette backup: CA 226
    Work number: ubmu0063_068_02
    Cantata no. 58: Ach Gott, wie manches Herzeleid. Ich bin vergnugt in meinem Leiden
    Duration: 7:06
    Cassette backup: CA 227
    Work number: ubmu0063_068_03
    Kammerkonzert fur Klavier und Geige mit dreizehn Blasern. Adagio
    Performers: Charles Haupt, violin; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 16:31
    Cassette backup: CA 228
    Work number: ubmu0063_068_04
    Der Hirt auf dem Felsen, D. 965
    Performers: Mary Beth Peil, soprano; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 12:45
    Cassette backup: CA 229
    Work number: ubmu0063_068_05
    Largo for violin, clarinet, and piano
    Duration: 7:09
    Cassette backup: CA 230
    Work number: ubmu0063_068_06
    Seiber, Matyas
    Drei Morgenstern Lieder (1929)
    Performers: Mary Beth Peil, soprano; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet
    Duration: 8:48
    Cassette backup: CA 231
    Work number: ubmu0063_068_07
    Bartok, Bala
    Contrasts for violin, clarinet, and piano
    Duration: 21:30
    Cassette backup: CA 232
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 39, April 16, 1969, 1 10-inch reel; Full-track mono, 7.5 ips (Box 7, Reel 069)
    Work number: ubmu0063_069_01
    Milan, Luis
    Pavane (1535)
    Duration: 1:38
    Cassette backup: CA 233
    Work number: ubmu0063_069_02
    Guerau, Francisco
    Canarios (1694)
    Duration: 1:33
    Cassette backup: CA 234
    Work number: ubmu0063_069_03
    Mudarra, Alonso
    Fantasia
    Duration: 2:10
    Cassette backup: CA 235
    Work number: ubmu0063_069_04
    Prelude, fugue, and allegro, harpsichord, BWV 998, arranged
    Cassette backup: CA 236
    Work number: ubmu0063_069_05
    Hiller, Lejaren
    Five Appalachian Ballads (1958)
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Jonathan Marcus, guitar
    Duration: 15:48
    Cassette backup: CA 237
    Work number: ubmu0063_069_06
    Matthews, Justus
    Two Miniatures (1968)
    Performers: Jonathan Marcus, guitar; Suzanne Mustard, violoncello
    Duration: 3:08
    Cassette backup: CA 238
    Note: Performed twice.
    Work number: ubmu0063_069_07
    Martin, Frank
    Quatre pieces breves (1933)
    Duration: 11:28
    Cassette backup: CA 239
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 40, April 30, 1969, 1 10-inch reel; Full-track mono, 7.5 ips (Box 7, Reel 070)
    Work number: ubmu0063_070_01
    Performers: Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Yoriko Takahashi Chodos, piano
    Duration: 12:35
    Cassette backup: CA 240
    Note: Program marked with altered order of works (correct in inventory)
    Work number: ubmu0063_070_02
    Kodaly, Zoltan
    Duo, violin, violoncello, op. 7
    Performers: Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello
    Duration: 28:25
    Cassette backup: CA 241
    Work number: ubmu0063_070_03
    Couperin, Francois
    Suite for two violoncelli
    Performers: Marijke Verberne, Robert Martin, violoncelli
    Duration: 14:38
    Cassette backup: CA 242
    Work number: ubmu0063_070_04
    Drei kleine Stucke, op. 11 (1914)
    Duration: 4:50
    Cassette backup: CA 243
    Work number: ubmu0063_070_05
    Andriessen, Hendrick
    Sonata for Violoncello Solo
    Performers: Marijke Verberne, violoncello
    Duration: 13:33
    Cassette backup: CA 244
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 41, November 24, 1969, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 7, Reel 071-072)
    Work number: ubmu0063_071_01
    Fitz, Richard
    Chamber Sonata (1965)
    Performers: Larry Stein, William Furioso, Richard Bisesi, Gerald Cash, Thomas Renzi, Paul Mouradian, percussion
    Duration: 9:06
    Cassette backup: CA 245
    Note: Note on program: "Right channel not recorded for several minutes".
    Work number: ubmu0063_071_02
    Negro, Ottavio
    Facets (1968)
    Performers: William Furioso, Richard Bisesi, Gerald Cash, Paul Mouradian, percussion
    Duration: 11:20
    Cassette backup: CA 246
    Work number: ubmu0063_071_03
    Sikorski, Tomasz
    Intersections (1968)
    Performers: Edward Burnham, Gerald Cash, Jan Williams, William Furioso, percussion
    Cassette backup: CA 247
    Work number: ubmu0063_071_04
    Fulkerson, James Orville
    Mobiles and Loops (1967)
    Performers: Abe McLarahmore, William Furioso, Gerald Cash, Thomas Renzi, percussion
    Duration: 18:57
    Cassette backup: CA 248
    Work number: ubmu0063_072_01
    Furioso, William
    Simon Says (1969)
    Performers: Bradd Gray, Thomas Renzi, Larry Stein, Abe McLarahmore, Paul Mouradian, Richard Bisesi, Gerald Cash, percussion; Ken Hafner, trumpet; Steve Winer, narrator; Edward Burnham, tape operator
    Duration: 24:00
    Cassette backup: CA 249
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 42, December 4, 1969, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 7, Reel 073)
    Work number: ubmu0063_073_01
    Levy, Burt
    Orbs with Flute
    Performers: Thomas Howell, flute
    Duration: 2:51
    Cassette backup: CA 250
    Work number: ubmu0063_073_02
    Brun, Herbert
    Gesto
    Performers: Thomas Howell, flute; Julius Eastman, piano
    Duration: 5:28
    Cassette backup: CA 251
    Work number: ubmu0063_073_03
    Gilbert, David
    Poem VI
    Performers: Thomas Howell, flute; Gerald Cash, William Furioso, percussion
    Cassette backup: CA 252
    Work number: ubmu0063_073_04
    Purswell, Patrick W.
    It Grew and Grew (1964)
    Cassette backup: CA 253
    Work number: ubmu0063_073_05
    Gaburo, Kenneth Louis
    Two
    Performers: Judith Sherman, mezzo soprano; Thomas Howell, alto flute; James Kurzdorfer, double bass
    Duration: 5:02
    Cassette backup: CA 254
    Work number: ubmu0063_073_06
    Howell, Thomas
    Thresholds II
    Duration: 4:55
    Cassette backup: CA 255
    Work number: ubmu0063_073_07
    Wolpe, Stefan
    Composition in Two Parts for flute and piano (1960)
    Duration: 16:50
    Cassette backup: CA 256
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 43, January 28, 1970, 3 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 7, Reel 074-076)
    Work number: ubmu0063_074_01
    Komorous, Rudolf
    Lady Blancarosa (1967)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, voice; Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Jacques Earley, actor
    Duration: 13:11
    Cassette backup: CA 257
    Work number: ubmu0063_075_01-04
    Journey to the End of the Night; Vertical thoughts III; Rabbi Akiba; For Franz Kline
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; instrumental ensemble, including John Heitmann, flute; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Edward Yadzinski, bass clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon
    Duration: 31:45
    Cassette backup: CA 258-261
    Work number: ubmu0063_076_01
    Cage, John; Cardew, Cornelius
    Forever and sunsmell (1944) performed with Schooltime Compositions (1967)
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Jacques Earley, actor; Julius Eastman, singer; James Fulkerson, trombone; Edward Burnham, Lynn Harbold, percussion; Cristyne Lawson, Carole Weiner, John Hall, dancers
    Duration: 33:04
    Cassette backup: CA 262A
    Note: Two works performed simultaneously.
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 44, February 4, 1970, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 7, Reel 077-078)
    Work number: ubmu0063_077_01
    Laneri, Roberto and Schiaffini, Giancarlo
    Night Brings a Rabbit (1969-70)
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Jan Williams, percussion
    Cassette backup: CA 263
    Work number: ubmu0063_077_02
    For Clarinet and percussion (1965)
    Cassette backup: CA 264
    Work number: ubmu0063_077_03
    Burge, David
    Sources III (1967)
    Duration: 15:39
    Cassette backup: CA 265
    Work number: ubmu0063_078_01
    Budd, Harold
    Lovely thing (piano) (1969)
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, piano
    Duration: 19:18
    Cassette backup: CA 266
    Note: 1st two works at 7 ½ ips; 3rd work at 15 ips
    Work number: ubmu0063_078_02
    Magnus Colorado (1969)
    Performers: Jan Williams, amplified gongs
    Duration: 10:49
    Cassette backup: CA 267
    Note: Includes introductory comments; Premiere performance.
    Work number: ubmu0063_078_03
    Black Flowers (1968)
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Jan Williams, percussion; Diane Williams, Mary Beth Peil, bells
    Duration: 9:46
    Cassette backup: CA 268
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 45, March 30, 1970, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 7, Reel 079)
    Work number: ubmu0063_079_01
    Grauer, Victor Asher
    But for the Rain
    Performers: Julius Eastman, piano
    Duration: 12:11
    Cassette backup: CA 269
    Work number: ubmu0063_079_02
    Davidovsky, Mario
    Synchronism III
    Performers: Marijke Verberne, violoncello; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 5:55
    Cassette backup: CA 270
    Work number: ubmu0063_079_03
    Silsbee, Ann Loomis
    Mirages
    Performers: Stephen Manes, quarter tone harpsichord; Marijke Verberne, violoncello
    Duration: 8:54
    Cassette backup: CA 271
    Work number: ubmu0063_079_04
    Corner, Philip
    Big Trombone
    Performers: James Fulkerson, bass trombone; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 9:34
    Cassette backup: CA 272
    Work number: ubmu0063_079_05
    Somers, Harrry Stuart
    Kuyas
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; John Heitmann, flute; Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 7:45
    Cassette backup: CA 273
    Work number: ubmu0063_079_06
    Kotik, Petr
    Puip
    Performers: Julius Eastman, speaker; George Ritscher, audio technician
    Duration: 13:39
    Cassette backup: CA 274
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 46, April 15, 1970, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 8, Reel 080-081)
    Work number: ubmu0063_080_01
    Cardew, Cornelius; Cage, John; Kotik, Petr
    Treatise (1967) with Aria and Fontana Mix and Music for 3
    Performers: All performed by: William Furioso, percussion; Petr Kotik, flute; Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Miroslav Vitous, double bass; Jan Williams, percussion; Diane Williams, viola; Mary Lane, violoncello
    Duration: 1:09:23
    Cassette backup: CA 275A
    Note: Three works performed simultaneously.
    Note: works 1-3 performed simultaneously?
    Work number: ubmu0063_081_01
    Olympia
    Performers: William Furioso, percussion; Petr Kotik, flute; Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Miroslav Vitous, double bass; Jan Williams, percussion; Diane Williams, viola; Mary Lane, violoncello
    Duration: 56:34
    Cassette backup: CA 276
    Note: Engineer's marking on program is ambiguous - check contents.
    Note: from inserted program it is difficult to tell if this tape only contains the 4th work or a continuation of the simultaneous performance of works 1-3
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 51, October 21, 1970, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo and mono., 7.5 ips (Box 8, Reel 082)
    Work number: ubmu0063_082_01
    Fulkerson, James
    Two Activities (1970)
    Performers: Members of the Center
    Duration: 22:00
    Cassette backup: CA 297
    Note: Format changes midway through tape
    Work number: ubmu0063_082_02
    5 Pages for Petr K. (1970)
    Performers: Marilyn Winterberg, dancer; S.E.M. Ensemble; Graham Weinbrenand Robert Friedman
    Cassette backup: CA 298
    Work number: ubmu0063_082_03
    Connections, directions and drones (1970)
    Duration: 34:18
    Cassette backup: CA 301
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 52, November 21, 1970, 1 10-inch reel (Box 8) and 1 7-inch reel (Box 2); Full-track mono, 7.5 ips; Note: Full program inserted with Tape 84. Program divided between Tape 83 and 84 - unclear which works are on which tape. (Box 8, 2, Reel 083-084)
    Work number: ubmu0063_083_01
    Unidentified composer
    Unidentified work
    Performers: Unknown
    Duration: 53:38
    Note: This sounds more like content from Concert April 15 1970, with simultaneous performance of Cardew, Cage, and Kotik.
    Note: The content of this performance is unclear; it does not correspond to the program, which is contained entirely on CA084. The recording of the performance ends at 55:30. After this, the tape contains another performance (starting in medias res) of Rudolf Komorous's Olympia (also contained on CA080), clearly with Julius Eastman as vocalist. It is not the same performance as that on CA080.
    Work number: ubmu0063_083_02
    Olympia (incomplete)
    Duration: 15:11
    Work number: ubmu0063_084_01
    Schwartz, Elliott
    Signals
    Performers: James Fulkerson, trombone, double bass
    Cassette backup: CA 303
    Work number: ubmu0063_084_02
    Brooks, William
    Poempiece II: How I Fooled the Armies (1969)
    Performers: James Fulkerson, trombone
    Duration: 10:12
    Cassette backup: CA 304
    Work number: ubmu0063_084_03
    Druckman, Jacob
    Animus I (1966)
    Performers: James Fulkerson trombone; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 13:13
    Cassette backup: CA 305
    Work number: ubmu0063_084_04
    Berio, Luciano
    Sequenza V (1966)
    Duration: 5:30
    Cassette backup: CA 306
    Work number: ubmu0063_084_05
    Big Trombone (1963)
    Performers: James Fulkerson, trombone; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 10:19
    Cassette backup: CA 307
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 54, March 26, 1971, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 8, Reel 085)
    Work number: ubmu0063_085_01
    Sonata, violin, piano, no. 4 (incomplete)
    Performers: Mark Sokol, violin; Roger Shields, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 309
    Note: First 1 ½ movements not recorded
    Work number: ubmu0063_085_02
    Piece in Two Parts for Violin Alone
    Performers: Mark Sokol, violin
    Duration: 13:05
    Cassette backup: CA 310
    Work number: ubmu0063_085_03
    Penderecki, Krzysztof
    Miniatures for Violin and piano
    Duration: 6:45
    Cassette backup: CA 311
    Work number: ubmu0063_085_04
    Four pieces for Violin and piano
    Cassette backup: CA 312
    Work number: ubmu0063_085_05
    Franck, Cesar
    Sonata, violin, piano, A major
    Duration: 30:25
    Cassette backup: CA 313
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 55, April 14, 1971, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 8, Reel 086)
    Work number: ubmu0063_086_01
    Prelude, Fugue and allegro, lute, BWV 988, E-flat major, arranged
    Performers: Stuart Fox, guitar
    Cassette backup: CA 314
    Work number: ubmu0063_086_02
    Tansman, Alexandre
    Cavatina (1951)
    Duration: 16:08
    Cassette backup: CA 315
    Work number: ubmu0063_086_03
    Matiegka, Wenzel and Schubert, Franz
    Nocturne, flute, viola, guitar, op. 21, G major, arranged
    Performers: Petr Kotik, flute; Jesse Levine, viola; Stuart Fox, guitar; Douglas Davis, violoncello
    Duration: 31:40
    Cassette backup: CA 316
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 56, April 17, 1971, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 8, Reel 087)
    Work number: ubmu0063_087_01
    Dallapiccola, Luigi
    Due Liriche Di Anacreonte (1944-45)
    Performers: Jane Holcombe, voice; Roberto Laneri, Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Jesse Levine, viola; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 5:40
    Cassette backup: CA 317
    Work number: ubmu0063_087_02
    Duration: 16:12
    Cassette backup: CA 318
    Work number: ubmu0063_087_03
    Prokofiev, Sergei Sergeevich
    Sonata, flute, piano, op. 94
    Performers: Petr Kotik, flute; Sumiko Kohno, piano
    Duration: 25:41
    Cassette backup: CA 319
    Work number: ubmu0063_087_04
    Contrasts for Violin, Clarinet and piano (1938)
    Performers: Mark Sokol, violin; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 19:08
    Cassette backup: CA 320
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 57, April 26, 1971, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track mono, 7.5 ips; Engineer's note: "One of the cannon to phono patchcord adaptors shorted out while using the Revox." (Box 8, Reel 088)
    Work number: ubmu0063_088_01
    Duo, viola, violoncello, WoO 32, E-flat major
    Performers: Jesse Levine, viola; Douglas Davis, violoncello
    Duration: 8:51
    Cassette backup: CA 321
    Work number: ubmu0063_088_02
    Hindemith, Paul
    Duet, viola, violoncello (1934)
    Cassette backup: CA 322
    Note: Engineer's note: "One of the cannon to phono patchcord adaptors shorted out while using the Revox."
    Work number: ubmu0063_088_03
    "A Frog He Went A-Courting": Variations on an English Nursery Song
    Performers: Douglas Davis, violoncello; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 6:46
    Cassette backup: CA 323
    Work number: ubmu0063_088_04
    Britten, Benjamin
    Sonata, violoncello, piano, op. 65, C major
    Performers: Douglas Davis, violoncello; Roger Shields. piano
    Cassette backup: CA 324
    Work number: ubmu0063_088_05
    Divertimento, violin, viola, violoncello, K. 563, E-flat major
    Performers: Charles Haupt, violin; Jesse Levine, viola; Douglas Davis, violoncello
    Duration: 45:52
    Cassette backup: CA 325
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 59, October 20, 1971, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 8, Reel 089-090)
    Work number: ubmu0063_089_01
    Levendosky, Charles
    Perimeters (a multimedia dramatization of a poem by Charles Levendosky)
    Performers: Elizabeth Axlerod, Linda Ciambella, Elizabeth Halsey, Gerald Lamarsh, Darleen Pickering, voices; dramatization by Frank Parman, Terry Moore; sound designed by Stuart Fox
    Duration: 59:27
    Cassette backup: CA 327A
    Note: Work performed two times. This is the 8:00 p.m. performance.
    Engineer's note: "Noise on right channel - strong throughout last 15 minutes"
    Work number: ubmu0063_090_01
    Duration: 59:05
    Cassette backup: CA 327B
    Note: Marked "Reel II", but contains complete, repeat performance
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 60, November 17, 1971, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 8, Reel 091)
    Work number: ubmu0063_091_01
    Francoeur, Francois
    Sonata, violoncello, continuo, E major
    Duration: 10:45
    Cassette backup: CA 328
    Work number: ubmu0063_091_02
    Funf Stucke im Volkston, violoncello, piano, op. 102
    Duration: 16:25
    Cassette backup: CA 329
    Work number: ubmu0063_091_03
    Sonata, violoncello alone, op. 25, no. 3
    Performers: Douglas Davis, violoncello
    Duration: 10:28
    Cassette backup: CA 330
    Work number: ubmu0063_091_04
    Duration: 11:30
    Cassette backup: CA 331
    Work number: ubmu0063_091_05
    Foss, Lukas
    Capriccio (1946)
    Duration: 6:25
    Cassette backup: CA 332
    Work number: ubmu0063_091_06
    Popper, David
    Dance of the Elves, op. 39
    Cassette backup: CA 333
    Work number: ubmu0063_091_07
    Chopin, Fredric
    Sonata, violoncello, piano, op. 65, G minor
    Duration: 4:43
    Cassette backup: CA 334
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 61, December 8, 1971, 1 7-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 2, Reel 092)
    Work number: ubmu0063_092_01
    Enriquez, Manuel
    Monologo (1971)
    Cassette backup: CA 335
    Engineer's note: "Other works were not recorded either because they were silent or totally pre-recorded."
    Work number: ubmu0063_092_02
    Erikson, Robert
    Ricercare a 5 (1971)
    Duration: 12:00
    Cassette backup: CA 336
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 62, February 20, 1972, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 9, Reel 093-094)
    Work number: ubmu0063_093_01
    Beethoven Tours "Sonata, piano, no. 6, B-flat major ("Rage over the lost composer")"
    Performers: Petr Kotik, flute; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Andrew Stiller, bassoon; Henry Rubin, violin; Roger Shields, piano
    Duration: 27:20
    Cassette backup: CA 339
    Note: Beethoven tours consists of "various selections from Beethoven's music". Not clear if there are marked divisions or if it is continuous.
    Work number: ubmu0063_094_01
    Performers: Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 8:07
    Cassette backup: CA 340
    Note: Check contents and compare to Cassettes CA 341-345.
    Work number: ubmu0063_094_02
    Beethoven Tours "Sonata, piano, no. 6, B-flat major ("Rage over the lost artifacts")"
    Performers: Michael Collier, piano
    Duration: 22:38
    Cassette backup: CA 341
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 63, February 23, 1972, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 9, Reel 095)
    Work number: ubmu0063_095_01
    Sonata, violin, piano, op. 12, no. 3, E-flat major
    Performers: Henry Rubin, violin; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 21:15
    Cassette backup: CA 346
    Work number: ubmu0063_095_02
    Fantasie in D major for Solo Violin
    Performers: Henry Rubin, violin
    Cassette backup: CA 347
    Work number: ubmu0063_095_03
    Falla, Manual de
    Suite Populaire Espagnole
    Cassette backup: CA 348
    Work number: ubmu0063_095_04
    Scherzo violin, piano, C minor
    Duration: 6:17
    Cassette backup: CA 349
    Work number: ubmu0063_095_05
    Sonata, violin, piano, op. 105, A minor
    Duration: 20:32
    Cassette backup: CA 350
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 64, March 8, 1972, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 9, Reel 096)
    Work number: ubmu0063_096_01
    Black Earth Percussion Group
    Improvisations
    Performers: Black Earth Percussion Group
    Duration: 7:54
    Cassette backup: CA 355
    Note: Tape played.
    Work number: ubmu0063_096_02
    Stockhausen, Karlheinz
    Refrain for Three Instrumentalists (1959)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, piano; woodblocks; Garry Kvistad, vibraphone, cowbells; Michael Collier, celesta, antique cymbals
    Duration: 15:16
    Cassette backup: CA 351
    Work number: ubmu0063_096_03
    Zyklus for one percussionist (1959) (Clockwise version--realized, 1972)
    Performers: Gary Kvistad, percussion
    Duration: 8:38
    Cassette backup: CA 352
    Work number: ubmu0063_096_04
    Memories of You (1964)
    Performers: Richard Trythall, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 353
    Work number: ubmu0063_096_05
    Kontakte
    Performers: Richard Trythall, piano, percussion; Garry Kvistad, percussion; George Ritscher, electronics
    Duration: 36:37
    Cassette backup: CA 355a
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 65, March 29, 1972, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 9, Reel 097-098)
    Work number: ubmu0063_097_01
    Mosaic (1964)
    Performers: Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Robert Winter, piano
    Duration: 16:21
    Cassette backup: CA 356
    Work number: ubmu0063_097_02
    Chadabe, Joel
    Street Scene (1967)
    Performers: Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Robert Winter, tape operator; tape realized by the composer
    Duration: 8:59
    Cassette backup: CA 357
    Work number: ubmu0063_097_03
    Villa-Rojo, Jesus
    Unos Resultados (1970)
    Performers: Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Carol Fortmeyer, Delmar Stewart, Leonard Matczynski, violas; Marsha Hassett, Wendel Haver, Shannon Snapp, violoncellos; Allen Dennis, double bass
    Duration: 15:36
    Cassette backup: CA 358
    Work number: ubmu0063_097_04
    Perle, George
    Sonata Quasi una Fantasia (1972)